https://ptfc.co.uk/site-information/cookie-privacy-policy/

Cookie & Privacy Policy
At ptfc.co.uk we are committed to protecting your privacy.
We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide a more personalised experience. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.
Any personal information provided or to be gathered by ptfc.co.uk is held by:
The Partick Thistle Football Club Ltd.
Firhill Stadium
80 Firhill Road
Glasgow
G20 7AL
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how we use and protect any information that you give us when you use this website. The terms ‘our’, ‘us’ or ‘we’ refers to Partick Thistle Football Club Ltd, the owner of this website. The term ‘you’ refers to the user or viewer of our website.
We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect through this site
We may collect the following information when you fill in a form on our web site:
Name and job title
Contact information including your email address
Demographic information such as postcode or preferences
Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or marketing
Information provided at the time of registering an account, purchasing services from us or requesting further services
Information when you report a problem with our site or the services you have purchased
Data retention
We only retain your personal data for as long as we need it to fulfil our business obligations, unless otherwise required by law. We will retain and use information to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements as follows:
Invoice data is kept for a minimum of 6 years (as required under UK Law).
Anonymous web site tracking data is retained for 26 months.
In addition we also retain the following information:
If you contact us by letter or email, records of the correspondence may be kept
Details of transactions you carry out through our site and of the fulfilment and administration of your orders
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts between you and us.
To improve our products and services.
We may send emails with information specifically relating to Partick Thistle Football Club or with information we think you might find useful or interesting.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which is placed on your computer’s hard drive. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. The cookies we use do not give us access to your computer or any information about you.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of some websites.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 2017-2019. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please contact us.
You can exercise your right to prevent any further marketing communication by following the unsubscribe link at the bottom of all promotional emails we send.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to us or email us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Site Terms
Cookie & Privacy Policy
Conditions of Sale
Keep up to date with all things Thistle
Subscribe Now
Site Terms
Cookie & Privacy Policy
Conditions of Sale
Copyright © 2020 Partick Thistle. All rights reserved.
Website by reflexblue.
